[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States of America"]}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "And you're comfortable with same-sex marriage now?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "'re", "comfortable", "with", "same-sex", "marriage", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "I -- look, I am vice president of the United States of America.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "look", ",", "I", "am", "vice", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", "of", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "I mean given the benefit of what -- of hindsight over the last 24 hours, do you still think that everything Joe Biden said is consistent with the president's position?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "given", "the", "benefit", "of", "what", "--", "of", "hindsight", "over", "the", "last", "24", "hours", ",", "do", "you", "still", "think", "that", "everything", "Joe", "Biden", "said", "is", "consistent", "with", "the", "president", "'s", "position", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", ":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "I feel, Piers, that on the policy that the vice president was describing there, that they are in complete accord.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", ",", "Piers", ",", "that", "on", "the", "policy", "that", "the", "vice", "president", "was", "describing", "there", ",", "that", "they", "are", "in", "complete", "accord", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 24 hours"], "PERSON": ["Joe Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "So why doesn't he just do it now?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "does", "n't", "he", "just", "do", "it", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, again, I'm not going to make news for the president here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "again", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "make", "news", "for", "the", "president", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "How big a danger does al Qaeda remain if we're still uncovering plots like this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "big", "a", "danger", "does", "al", "Qaeda", "remain", "if", "we", "'re", "still", "uncovering", "plots", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Well, Piers, I don't know the -- I know what you know about the details of this particular case.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "the", "--", "I", "know", "what", "you", "know", "about", "the", "details", "of", "this", "particular", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Great Depression"]}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ":", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RBS", ":", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Is that the kind of theme that you'll be looking to press for the campaign?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "kind", "of", "theme", "that", "you", "'ll", "be", "looking", "to", "press", "for", "the", "campaign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "Well, the -- look, there's no question that we are coming back from the most -- the most vicious, the deepest recession since the Great Depression.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "--", "look", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "question", "that", "we", "are", "coming", "back", "from", "the", "most", "--", "the", "most", "vicious", ",", "the", "deepest", "recession", "since", "the", "Great", "Depression", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Biden"]}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "What did you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Well, I made of it that Vice President Biden, you know, had a policy break from the president.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "made", "of", "it", "that", "Vice", "President", "Biden", ",", "you", "know", ",", "had", "a", "policy", "break", "from", "the", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Is it not better to be a bit more progressive, especially now your man has won the nomination, or effectively won it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "not", "better", "to", "be", "a", "bit", "more", "progressive", ",", "especially", "now", "your", "man", "has", "won", "the", "nomination", ",", "or", "effectively", "won", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RBR", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Well, you know, people's beliefs are their beliefs, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "people", "'s", "beliefs", "are", "their", "beliefs", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "It's not sustainable to say you're worse off, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "sustainable", "to", "say", "you", "'re", "worse", "off", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, Piers, the numbers I just cited, you know, are accurate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "the", "numbers", "I", "just", "cited", ",", "you", "know", ",", "are", "accurate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "Which way are you guys heading?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "way", "are", "you", "guys", "heading", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Well, you know, the fact is, this is a lengthy process.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "fact", "is", ",", "this", "is", "a", "lengthy", "process", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Did you go along with that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "go", "along", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Sounded like a lot of people I knew on the court.", "answer_tokens": ["Sounded", "like", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "I", "knew", "on", "the", "court", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Is he really?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Yes, that's right.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "I don't feel that much different in age from him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "feel", "that", "much", "different", "in", "age", "from", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ",", "CC", ":", "IN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "But she found that women and men are starting to lose their sex drives much earlier than they used to, and -- because of stress and toxicity and normal aging.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "she", "found", "that", "women", "and", "men", "are", "starting", "to", "lose", "their", "sex", "drives", "much", "earlier", "than", "they", "used", "to", ",", "and", "--", "because", "of", "stress", "and", "toxicity", "and", "normal", "aging", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Did you ever see \"Threes Company\" or were you over in England?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "see", "``", "Threes", "Company", "''", "or", "were", "you", "over", "in", "England", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "``", "NNS", "NNP", "''", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "I could lie.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "could", "lie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "-- fascinated by somebody bursting with vitality like you and energy and positive thoughts could actually have a 30 years feud?", "question_tokens": ["--", "fascinated", "by", "somebody", "bursting", "with", "vitality", "like", "you", "and", "energy", "and", "positive", "thoughts", "could", "actually", "have", "a", "30", "years", "feud", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "You know, such a long story.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "such", "a", "long", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120507pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "What's the short version?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "short", "version", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "I was fired for asking to be paid commensurate with the men.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "fired", "for", "asking", "to", "be", "paid", "commensurate", "with", "the", "men", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]